<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Amazon Connect SI Onboarding Workshop</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Amazon Connect SI Onboarding Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Primer on Amazon Connect</title>
      <link>/10_first_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/10_first_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Access for this course requires logging into the APN Partner Central. The completion of this course will be associated with your APN credentials.
 Course Objectives  Configure a cloud-based contact center using Amazon Connect. Identify architectural components of the caller version Launch an Amazon Connect instance. Design an interactive voice response (IVR) system using the graphical editor within Amazon Connect. Integrate Amazon Connect with different AWS services including AWS IAM, AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Lex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/20_second_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/20_second_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case There are several scenarios in which your Contact Center Operations team will need to change the messaging within their IVR or change how routing is handled. For example, if there is a hurricane that requires a contact center to close, both the messaging and the hours of operation will need to be adjusted.
Integrated Services  Amazon Connect CloudFormation DynamoDB Lambda CloudWatch  Training Online Training: Emergency and Holiday Routing with Dynamic Messaging</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/30_third_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/30_third_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case Amazon Connect enables a chat channel that uses the same contact flows as the voice channel. In a truly omni-channel design, the only distinction between a chat interaction and a voice interaction is the field &amp;ldquo;channel&amp;rdquo; in the data.
To deploy Chat for your customers, you not only need to enable it in the routing profiles and in the contact flows, you also need to enable the ingress of the chat conversation, which is usually your customer&amp;rsquo;s webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/40_fourth_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/40_fourth_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case Contact Center data is a critical requirement for our customers. In legacy solutions, customers were constrained to whatever reporting platform came with the ACD. Amazon Connect shifts that paradigm. The data that is generated from Amazon Connect belongs to the customer to do whatever they want with.
Amazon Connect delivers data in a myriad of ways. Customers can access both historical and realtime data through the Connect UI. That data can be exported, scheduled, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/50_fifth_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/50_fifth_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case As Contact Center Technology professionals, we understand the importance of call deflection, qualifying the caller, and automation. While the use of bots to enable this functionality has become the norm, there are many use cases that require an advanced approach.
Integrated Services  Amazon Connect Amazon Lex DynamoDB Lambda  Training Online Training: Build a Better Bot
PDF of Online Course: Build a Better Bot PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/60_sixth_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/60_sixth_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case As a Solutions Implementor, our role is not only to build innovative customer service experiences, it&amp;rsquo;s also to facilitate our customers being able to sustain the technology. A critical part of that effort is triaging issues that arise.
Integrated Services  Amazon Connect CloudWatch DynamoDB Lambda  Training Online Training: Troubleshooting with CloudWatch
PDF of Online Course: Troubleshooting with CloudWatch PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/70_seventh_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/70_seventh_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case Often, the out-of-the-box CCP will not meet the requirements of your customer.
Integrated Services  Amazon Connect CloudFormation Lambda  GitHub Resources Amazon Connect Streams
Training Online Training: Build a Custom CCP
PDF of Online Course: Build a Custom CCP PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/80_eighth_section/1_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80_eighth_section/1_page.html</guid>
      <description>Use Case As trusted partners in the AWS Partner Network, we rely on you to deliver the same level of customer obsession that we practice. To that end, there are best practices that team of Amazon Connect Solution Architects have written to help you exceed your customer&amp;rsquo;s expectations.
Training Online Training: Amazon Connect Best Practices
PDF of Online Course: Amazon Connect Best Practices PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/20_second_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/20_second_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  Connect Case Studies  Intuit Axial Health Care Capital One  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/30_third_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/30_third_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Amazon Connect Chat Admin Guide Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  Relevant Blogs  Using Amazon Connect and Amazon Lex to build a Web Chat  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/40_fourth_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/40_fourth_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Quick Start for Streaming Amazon Connect Data to Redshift Amazon Connect Metrics and Contact Trace Records Contact Trace Records Data Model Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/50_fifth_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/50_fifth_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  Relevant Blogs  Updating your addresses with Amazon Connect and Amazon Lex Integrating WhatsApp using Amazon Lex and Amazon Connect Using Amazon Connect and Amazon Lex to build a Web Chat  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/60_sixth_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/60_sixth_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/70_seventh_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/70_seventh_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/80_eighth_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80_eighth_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation  Connect Admin Guide Connect API Reference SDK &amp;amp; Developer Tools Lambda Documentation DynamoDB Documentation Quotas Reference Architectures  Connect Case Studies  Intuit Axial Health Care Capital One  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional Resources for Integrated Services</title>
      <link>/10_first_section/2_page.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/10_first_section/2_page.html</guid>
      <description>AWS Lambda Foundations Amazon DynamoDB Service Primer </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>